

KAJA CIEŚLICZKA

Tel. 509 599 655

Mail: kajka.c@gmail.com

Check out my web CV version

Hello world! I'm Kaja - I work as a Product Development Junior Specialist and PO support in the development of two awesome mobile applications. My leading talents are: Learner, Empathy and Woo @CliftonStrengths™. Thanks to them I am a person who loves to learn and acquire new skills. My empathy allows me to understand the client's needs and my woo makes communication simple and enjoyable. I hope that we will have the opportunity to talk and get to know each other better.

COURSES & WORKSHOPS

GIRLS FOR GIRLS - NOKIA WORKSHOPS

Learn about software testing, version control system - Git and delving into the Agile methodology.

RAILS GIRLS POZNAŃ - WORKSHOPS

Learn beck-end development with best Ruby's mentor - Kasia Bernad. Code simple budget planner application using the Ruby on Rails framework.

UDEMY - FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT COURSES

Build styled, well-structured websites. Learn how to use HTML5 standard to create websites. Understand CSS syntax, selectors, and units. Acquire the basic knowledge of JavaScript.

SKILLS

Good knowledge

HTML CSS Emmet

Basic knowledge

JavaScript & jQuery Bootstrap 4 Ruby & Ruby on Rails SQL

Other

Jira Scrum

Languages

Polish - Native speaker

English - Upper-Intermediate - B2/C1

Italian - Elementary / Communicative - A2

EDUCATION

2018-2019 Wyższa Szkoła Bankowa

Postgraduate studies - Front-end programming with Angular

2011-2013 University of Wroclaw

Masters Degree of Biotechnology

EXPERIENCE

07.2018-Present Trans.eu

Position: Product Developmnet Junior Specialist

PO support in the development of mobile applications Cooperation with a development team Work in agile methodologies (Scrum)

04.2014-06.2018 Colgate-Palmolive, WIF Wrocław, Macopharma

Position: Microbiologist

Testing of microbiological load of products
Microbiological examination of water (membrane filtration)
Bacterial diagnosis

HOBBY

- Baking & Cooking
- 'Absorbing books'
- Handmade
- Kettlebell